welcome everybody to spooky tales with
manic and knuckles
unfortunately my pal knucks couldn't
make it today but that's all right
because my brother's boyfriend bartelby
is letting me tell my spooky story for
you over at has trillion dollar mansion
when are you going home i don't like you
in my house
so kick back relax and grab some candy
corn because we are not wasting any more
time
bart levy would you like to start us off
no
okay here we go
it was a typically bright sunny morning
the cool fall air was blowing through
the town and the trees were turning
beautiful shapes of oranges and reds
sonic enjoyed this comfy hot chocolate
drinking weather
as he walked over to has friends at
their local gathering spot the park just
on the east end of town where all the
cool kids were eating pizza hut pizza
the ever so slightly chubby hedgehog boy
was greeted with a chorus of greetings
from the four sitting around the picnic
table they were his twin siblings sonia
and manic their friend knuckles the
echidna he was red
and the local babe mendela tour who
manic was hitting ever since elementary
school
how's everyone doing sonic asked
well my birthday was last week and my
dad bought me mindy started to say
before knuckles cut her off
nobody cares what you have to say you
are just a
everybody agreed so mindy went back to
eating her tuna salad sandwich
[Music]
hey how about those weird crop circle
things they found in the corn fields
last night
anybody here about those
sonja asked the group
crop circles the blue hedgehog
questioned his curiosity peaked
yeah everybody has been talking about it
at school nobody knows how they got
there
sonic silently sipped from his apple
juice
while the rest of his friends continued
their talks of the strange phenomenon
[Music]
sonic was always fascinated by the
possibility of beings from outer space
ever since he was a baby with a
big ass
his mother would read him picture books
about rocket ships
he had always dreamed of going to outer
space one day or maybe join nasa when he
grew larger
but there was always one thing stopping
him
it was fear
fear of the
unknown fear of aliens
but they can't be real can they
i don't know
so fatty are you in or not
the echidna said nudging sonic slightly
with his elbow
up
we're going to spend the night at the
cornfield tonight maybe we can spot
those aliens
no way sonic said to his green bro
it's probably just some prankster
but what if it's not
sonic knew his friends were only kidding
but what if it was all real
should he really take this risk
what if there really are aliens no it's
now or never
it was time for sonic to conquer his
fear of aliens
and hopefully prove once and for all
that aliens don't exist
that way sonic can finally become the
astronaut he always wanted to be
sonic gave his friends a thumbs up
and with that the operation was underway
everyone was leaving to head off to the
cornfields when suddenly
a beautiful man in a full body jumpsuit
caught sonic's eyes his odd uniform
reflected the sun almost as if it was
made out of pure aluminum foil
it was simply eye-catching don't go to
the cornfield tonight was all he said
sonic thought this guy was sexy but
weird he wouldn't let this man's words
deter him from doing what was right
even if he did want to get in
that ass by him
sonic wished the strange man a good day
and left immediately to join his friends
later that night sonic and the rest of
his friends arrived in the spooky
cornfield
nothing seemed to be out of the ordinary
at least as far as they could see
the crew looked at one another unsure of
what to say
eventually manic spoke up
we should take turns going to sleep he
said we will cycle throughout the night
that way if anything happens we'll know
about it
it was decided
sonic and manic would stay up as the
lookout for the first four hours and
then they will switch off
but alas that would not be
[Music]
for only moments later the hedgehog bros
could have sworn they heard something
it sounded strange
as if it was a spacecraft of another
world
bro what is that sonic said
it's it's just a plane bro don't worry
about it
no this was something very very
different
manic was stunned with fear
sonic was also scared then almost out of
nowhere a flying saucer came flying
through the clouds at great speed
sonic could both hear and smell that
manic pooped in his pants
especially when the alien man emerged
from the cockpit of his spacecraft he
was carrying a red gun and shot quickly
at manic while calling him a
he was lifted into the air and was
vaporized on the spot
there was little more than dust by the
time the sexy spaceman put his ray gun
away
i told you not to come here
sonic knew he had to act but he just
couldn't
he was paralyzed with fear and not only
that
but stunned by this man's beauty and
because his butt was so big
the beautiful blonde man smoked knowing
full well what sonic wanted
you want to climb aboard my flying
saucer so i could take you for a ride
and spank you is that it
no well maybe sonic stuttered out
bart levy liked that
he knew at that very moment that he was
going to claim the man as his
bart levy climbed back into his
spaceship and activated the tractor beam
what's happening
sonic screamed as he was being lifted
off the ground and toured the spacecraft
someone saved me
but no one did
there was no doubt about it now
sonic knew aliens are real
[Music]
well that's it
did you enjoy the story
i guess
what about your little brother did he
like it too
i guess
then get out of my house now i just
bought a mcflurry and cheesy gold beater
crunch with a new hip delivery app da
dash and i do not wish to be seen
conversing with you poor people when the
delivery man arrives
isn't doordash expensive
not when you're rich
[Music]
do
me
[Music]